Thomas Wiltshire

Hello, my name is Thomas. I'm a hard-working, passionate games programmer that is currently living in Ballarat, Victoria. Over the last 3 years, I have been studying at the Academy of Interactive Entertainment (AIE) to obtain a Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds (Programming).

Fraser Street Mount Pleasant, VIC 3350

+64 466661042 thomas.wiltshire14@icloud.com thomaswiltshire.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds, Academy of Interactive Entertainment — *Melbourne*, *Victoria*

January 2017 - December 2019

Primary School / High School, Kyabram P-12 College / Kyabram St Augustine's College — *Kyabram, Victoria*

January 2002 - December 2014

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Trainee, Advance Computing — *Kyabram, Victoria*

January 2016 - December 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at Advance Computing for around a year where I started a Certificate 3 in Information Technology as a part of my traineeship in software development. I learnt a lot during my time at Advance, had many amazing experiences, obtained a greater knowledge of business and got my first real taste of the software development industry.

Kitchen Crew Member, Mc Donald's Australia — *Echuca*, *Victoria*

March 2015 - January 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at McDonald's Echuca within the kitchen environment, being trained in most aspects. During my time here, I gained irreplaceable skills and experience in teamwork, punctuality, leadership and of course, cleaning and cooking.

IT Technicians Assistant (Work Placement), Kyabram Community and Learning Centre — *Kyabram, Victoria*

March 2014 - December 2014 (½ Year)

As a part of my VCAL studies, we were required to find work placement positions for at least one day a week. I worked at KCLC in the IT department helping with various repair jobs, network issues and general computer assistance.

EXPERIENCE AND SKILLS

Software Development. C#, C++, Lua, HTML/CSS, UWP.

Agile Development Methodology.

Git and Git Terminal Experience.

Knowledge in both PC and Macintosh systems.

Punctual, Polite and Enthusiastic.

Teamwork and Troubleshooting Skills and Experience.

NOTABLE PROJECTS (FOUND AT THOMASWILTSHIRE.COM)

Zombie Game - Video Game.

Toy Wars - Video Game.

Gypsy's Tale - Video Game / Technical Design Document.

REFERENCES

AS THIS IS A PUBLIC SITE, REFERENCES ARE AVAILABLE ON REQUEST TO PROTECT REFERENCE INFORMATION!